http://www.brooksbandits.ca/tickets/privacy-policy.html

Billets
Hockey Fans in Training (HockeyFIT)
Billets
Hockey Fans in Training (HockeyFIT)
Billets
Hockey Fans in Training (HockeyFIT)
Billets
Hockey Fans in Training (HockeyFIT)
Privacy Policy
You may visit our site anonymously. Information is collected from you only when you register for the e-newsletter, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
We may use the information we collect: to personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested; to allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests; improve your game day experience; to quickly process your transactions; and to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we occasionally send out newsletters to update you on the lastest news, products, special offers, and events.  If you wish to subscribe to our e-newsletter, send an email to bbmarketing@eidnet.org with the subject “subscribe”. You can find an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on July 30, 2013.
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue to bbmarketing@eidnet.org.
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
[webtv_image] => Copy of Copy of Copy of 2020-21 cash raffle (2).png
[youtube_url] => https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWLQ8-MZHSg444xg1PdZmyw
)
)
